<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2015, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 15:04:31 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 15:04:31 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>Apple Reports Record Third Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/07/21Apple-Reports-Record-Third-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2015 third quarter ended June 27. The company posted quarterly revenue of $49.6 billion and quarterly net profit of $10.7 billion, or $1.85 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $37.4 billion and net profit of $7.7 billion, or $1.28 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 39.7 percent compared to 39.4 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 64 percent of the quarter’s revenue. The growth was fueled by record third-quarter sales of iPhone and Mac, all-time record revenue from services, and the successful launch of Apple Watch. “We had an amazing quarter, with iPhone revenue up 59 percent over last year, strong sales of Mac, all-time record revenue from services, driven by the App Store, and a great start for Apple Watch,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “The excitement for Apple Music has been incredible, and we’re looking forward to releasing iOS 9, OS X El Capitan, and watchOS 2 to customers in the fall.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 14:29:30 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces Best iPod touch Yet</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/07/15Apple-Introduces-The-Best-iPod-touch-Yet.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has introduced the best iPod touch yet and unveiled a new lineup of colors for all iPod models, including space gray, silver, gold, pink, and blue. The iPod touch features a new 8-megapixel iSight camera, an improved FaceTime HD camera, the Apple-designed A8 chip, and even better fitness tracking with the M8 motion coprocessor. “iPod touch gives customers around the world access to Apple Music, the App Store, and iOS, the world’s most advanced mobile operating system, starting at just $199,” said Greg Joswiak, Apple’s vice president of iPhone, iPod, and iOS Product Marketing. “With big advancements like the A8 chip and the 8-megapixel iSight camera, customers can experience next-level gameplay, take even more beautiful photos and enjoy their favorite music, TV shows, and movies.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 15:12:23 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Introducing Apple Music — All The Ways You Love Music. All in One Place.</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Introducing-Apple-Music-All-The-Ways-You-Love-Music-All-in-One-Place-.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled Apple Music, a single, intuitive app that combines the best ways to enjoy music — all in one place. Apple Music is a streaming music service, a worldwide live radio station broadcasting 24 hours a day, and a new way for music fans to connect with their favorite artists. Apple Music combines the largest and most diverse collection of music with the expertise of world-class experts who have programmed playlists for your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, Mac, PC, Apple TV, and Android phones. Apple Music will be available starting June 30 in over 100 countries. “We love music, and the new Apple Music service puts an incredible experience at every fan’s fingertips,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “All the ways people love enjoying music come together in one app — a revolutionary streaming service, live worldwide radio, and an exciting way for fans to connect with artists.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:55:49 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Previews iOS 9</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Previews-iOS-9.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled iOS 9, giving a preview of new iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch software that will be available this fall. In this upcoming release, iOS devices become more intelligent and proactive with powerful search and improved Siri features — all without compromising users’ privacy. New multitasking features designed specifically for iPad allow you to work with two apps simultaneously, side-by-side, or with the new Picture-in-Picture feature, to keep watching a video while browsing the web, composing email, or using any other app. “iOS 9 is packed with more intelligence throughout, and delivers big updates to the apps customers use most — Maps supports public transit, a redesigned Notes app provides great new ways to capture ideas, and a beautiful News app delivers content that’s personalized to your interests,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering. “With our new iPad features, users can take advantage of the power of iPad, working in two apps at the same time with Split View, Slide Over, or Picture-in-Picture.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:52:57 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces News App for iPhone and iPad</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Announces-News-App-for-iPhone-iPad.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled an all-new News app delivering the best news reading experience on any mobile device. Available with iOS 9 this fall for iPhone and iPad, News combines the visually rich layout of a magazine with the immediacy and customization of digital media. News follows over a million topics and pulls relevant stories based on your specific interests that can be easily shared or saved for later. News is powered by the new custom-designed Apple News Format, a digital publishing format that allows publishers to create beautiful layouts. “News seamlessly delivers the articles you want to read in a beautiful and uncluttered format, while respecting your privacy, because Apple doesn’t share your personal data,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “We already have nearly 20 publishers representing more than 50 titles joining us, including Condé Nast, ESPN, The New York Times, Hearst, Time Inc., CNN, and Bloomberg.” </description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:51:42 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces OS X El Capitan</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Announces-OS-X-El-Capitan-with-Refined-Experience-Improved-Performance.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced OS X El Capitan, a new version of OS X that refines the Mac experience and improves system performance. Building on last year’s release of OS X Yosemite, El Capitan introduces enhancements to window management, built-in apps, and Spotlight search, and makes everyday activities faster and more responsive. Metal, Apple’s breakthrough graphics technology, is integrated into El Capitan, delivering systemwide performance gains and enabling games and pro apps to tap into the full power of Mac graphics processors. “OS X delivers unparalleled integration between Mac hardware, iOS devices, apps, and online services, and has helped Mac sales outpace the PC industry every year for the last decade,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering. “Customers loved last year’s landmark OS X Yosemite release and made it the fastest-adopted PC operating system ever. With El Capitan, we’re further refining the Mac experience with enhancements to window management, Spotlight, and built-in apps, and improving performance so everyday activities — from launching apps to accessing email — are faster and more responsive.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:50:35 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Previews New Apple Watch Software</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Previews-New-Apple-Watch-Software.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today previewed watchOS 2, the first major software update for Apple Watch, giving developers the tools to build faster and more powerful apps running natively on Apple Watch. Starting today, developers can take advantage of innovative hardware features of Apple Watch including the Digital Crown, Taptic Engine, and heart rate sensor, along with software APIs to build new app experiences. Available to Apple Watch users this fall, watchOS 2 also includes new watch faces, third-party app information as watch face complications, and new communication capabilities in Mail, Friends, and Digital Touch. “We are thrilled with the feedback we’re getting from Apple Watch customers, and after just a few weeks of availability we’re excited for developers to start building native apps for watchOS 2,” said Kevin Lynch, Apple’s vice president of Technology. “We think Apple Watch users will love being able to see information from their favorite apps right on the watch face, and enjoy the many new experiences developers will dream up now that they have access to even more innovative features of Apple Watch.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:49:29 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Pay Giving Shoppers Even More Ways to Pay</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Pay-Giving-Shoppers-Even-More-Ways-to-Pay.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced Apple Pay is adding support for rewards programs and store-issued credit and debit cards with iOS 9. Apple Pay will also give shoppers more ways to pay in the U.S., expanding merchant acceptance to over one million locations next month and bringing support for Discover this fall. With this addition, Apple Pay will accept credit and debit cards across all major card networks, issued by the most popular banks, representing 98 percent of all credit card purchase volume in the U.S. “Apple Pay has kicked off a new era of payments and our users love the incredibly easy, secure, and private way to pay,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “We’re bringing our customers the most requested features with support for rewards and store-issued cards, and expanding how and where Apple Pay is accepted, which truly transforms the way people pay.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:48:41 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Pay Coming to the UK</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/06/08Apple-Pay-Coming-to-the-UK.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that starting next month, Apple Pay will be available to customers in the UK, bringing them the easy, secure and private way to pay. At launch, over 250,000 locations will accept Apple Pay, with support from eight of the UK’s most established banks, across all of the major credit and debit card networks. “We’re thrilled to bring Apple Pay to the UK with support at launch from the most popular banks, an incredible roster of merchants, and many of our users’ favorite apps.” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 13:46:09 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces 15-inch MacBook Pro with Force Touch Trackpad and New $1999 iMac with Retina 5K Display</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/05/19Apple-Introduces-15-inch-MacBook-Pro-with-Force-Touch-Trackpad-New-1-999-iMac-with-Retina-5K-Display.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today updated the 15-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display with the new Force Touch trackpad, faster flash storage, longer battery life, and faster discrete graphics. Apple also introduced a new $1,999 configuration of the 27-inch iMac with Retina 5K display featuring a 14.7 million pixel display, quad-core processors, and AMD graphics, and lowered the price of the top-end iMac to $2,299. “The response to the new MacBook and updated 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display has been amazing, and today we are thrilled to bring the new Force Touch trackpad, faster flash storage, and longer battery life to the 15-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “Customers love the groundbreaking iMac with Retina 5K display, and now with a new lower starting price, even more people can experience the best desktop we’ve ever made.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 11:41:34 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces New Environmental Initiatives in China</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/05/11Apple-Announces-New-Environmental-Initiatives-in-China.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced an expansion of its renewable energy and environmental protection initiatives in China, including a new multiyear project with World Wildlife Fund to significantly increase responsibly managed forests across China. The new program aims to protect as much as 1 million acres of responsibly managed working forests that provide fiber for pulp, paper, and wood products. “Forests, like energy, can be renewable resources,” said Lisa Jackson, Apple’s vice president of Environmental Initiatives. “We believe we can run on naturally renewable resources and ensure that we protect — and create — as much sustainable working forest as needed to produce the virgin paper in our product packaging.” Apple also announced its intent to expand its industry-leading renewable energy projects to manufacturing facilities in China.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 11:37:08 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Record Second Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/04/27Apple-Reports-Record-Second-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced financial results for its fiscal 2015 second quarter ended March 28. The company posted quarterly revenue of $58 billion and quarterly net profit of $13.6 billion, or $2.33 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $45.6 billion and net profit of $10.2 billion, or $1.66 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 40.8 percent compared to 39.3 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 69 percent of the quarter’s revenue. “We are thrilled by the continued strength of iPhone, Mac, and the App Store, which drove our best March quarter results ever,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We’re seeing a higher rate of people switching to iPhone than we’ve experienced in previous cycles, and we’re off to an exciting start to the June quarter with the launch of Apple Watch.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 13:58:08 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Expands Capital Return Program to $200 Billion</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/04/27Apple-Expands-Capital-Return-Program-to-200-Billion.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that its board of directors has authorized an increase of more than 50 percent to the company’s program to return capital to shareholders. Under the expanded program, Apple plans to utilize a cumulative total of $200 billion of cash by the end of March 2017. As part of the revised program, the board has increased its share repurchase authorization to $140 billion from the $90 billion level announced last year. In addition, the company expects to continue to net-share-settle vesting restricted stock units. The board has also approved an increase of 11 percent to the company’s quarterly dividend, and has declared a dividend of $0.52 per share, payable on May 14, 2015, to shareholders of record as of the close of business on May 11. “We believe Apple has a bright future ahead, and the unprecedented size of our capital return program reflects that strong confidence,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “While most of our program will focus on buying back shares, we know that the dividend is very important to many of our investors, so we’re raising it for the third time in less than three years.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 13:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple’s Worldwide Developers Conference Kicks Off June 8</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/04/14Apples-Worldwide-Developers-Conference-Kicks-Off-June-8-at-San-Franciscos-Moscone-West.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced it will hold its 26th annual Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) June 8 through June 12 at San Francisco’s Moscone West, with more sessions than ever before streamed live to developers worldwide. WWDC will feature more than 100 technical sessions, over 1,000 Apple engineers, hands-on labs, and the Apple Design Awards. “The App Store ignited an app ecosystem that is simply amazing, forever changing the lives of customers and creating millions of jobs worldwide,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “We’ve got incredible new technologies for iOS and OS X to share with developers at WWDC and around the world, and can’t wait to see the next generation of apps they create.” </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 14:10:14 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces ResearchKit Available to Medical Researchers</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/04/14Apple-Announces-ResearchKit-Available-Today-to-Medical-Researchers.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that ResearchKit, a software framework designed for medical and health research, is now available. Medical researchers will be able to use ResearchKit to develop their own apps, and developers can also contribute new research modules to the open source framework. “We are delighted and encouraged by the response to ResearchKit from the medical and research community and the participants contributing to medical research. Studies that historically attracted a few hundred participants are now attracting participants in the tens of thousands,” said Jeff Williams, Apple’s senior vice president of Operations. “Medical researchers all over the world are actively exploring how ResearchKit can help them study even more diseases, and we believe the impact on global understanding of health and wellness will be profound.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 14:04:23 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Updates Final Cut Pro X, Motion, and Compressor</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/04/13Apple-Updates-Final-Cut-Pro-X-Motion-and-Compressor.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated Final Cut Pro X, Motion, and Compressor with new features for motion graphics and key enhancements to accelerate video editing, packaging, and delivery. Final Cut Pro 10.2 introduces stunning 3D titles that are easy to use, improved masking for color grading and effects, native support for more camera formats, and GPU-accelerated RED RAW processing. Motion 5.2 extends the power of 3D titles with the ability to create custom materials and environments and instantly publish them to Final Cut Pro X. Compressor 4.2 makes it easy to package a movie for sale on the iTunes Store. “From Hollywood blockbuster directors to first-time movie makers, Final Cut Pro X is changing the way we edit movies today,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 14:00:54 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Watch Available in Nine Countries on April 24</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/watch/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that Apple Watch will be available April 24 to customers in Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, the UK, and the U.S. Apple Watch brings an entirely new way to receive information at a glance and interact with the world through third-party apps designed specifically for the wrist. “Apple Watch begins a new chapter in the way we relate to technology and we think our customers are going to love it,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We can’t wait for people to start wearing Apple Watch to easily access information that matters, to interact with the world, and to live a better day by being more aware of their daily activity than ever before.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:11:20 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Unveils All-New MacBook</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/macbook/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled the all-new MacBook, a thinner and lighter line of notebooks available in gold, silver, and space gray aluminum finishes. MacBook features a 12-inch Retina display; a full-size keyboard; the all-new Force Touch trackpad; a compact USB-C port for data transfer, video out, and charging in a single connector; and a new battery designed to deliver all-day life. “Apple has reinvented the notebook with the new MacBook, and at just 2 pounds and 13.1 millimeters, it’s the thinnest and lightest Mac ever,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “Every component of the MacBook reveals a new innovation. From its fanless design, ultrathin Retina display, and full-size keyboard that’s 34 percent thinner, to its all-new Force Touch trackpad, versatile USB-C port, and breakthrough terraced battery design, the new MacBook is the future of the notebook.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:09:51 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Updates 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina Display and MacBook Air</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/03/09Apple-Updates-13-inch-MacBook-Pro-with-Retina-Display-MacBook-Air.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated the 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display and the 11-inch and 13-inch MacBook Air. “Today, the popular 13-inch MacBook Pro with Retina display, 11-inch MacBook Air and 13-inch MacBook Air all received significant upgrades,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “The 13-inch MacBook Pro has been updated with the latest processors, more powerful graphics, faster flash, longer battery life, and the all-new Force Touch trackpad. We’re also bringing the latest processors and graphics and faster Thunderbolt 2 to the 11-inch and 13-inch MacBook Air, as well as up to two times faster flash to the 13-inch MacBook Air.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:08:29 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces ResearchKit, Giving Medical Researchers New Tools</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/researchkit/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced ResearchKit, an open-source software framework designed for medical and health research that can help doctors and scientists gather data more frequently and more accurately from participants using iPhone apps. World-class research institutions have already developed apps with ResearchKit for studies on asthma, breast cancer, cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and Parkinson’s disease. “iOS apps already help millions of customers track and improve their health. With hundreds of millions of iPhones in use around the world, we saw an opportunity for Apple to have an even greater impact by empowering people to participate in and contribute to medical research,” said Jeff Williams, Apple’s senior vice president of Operations. “ResearchKit gives the scientific community access to a diverse, global population and more ways to collect data than ever before.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:07:41 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>